nyne.com 2015-10-09

# Privacy Policy - Nyne Multimedia

**PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. WHEN YOU USE THIS WEBSITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTOOD, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE POLICIES, TERMS, AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH HEREIN.**  

**ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY**

NYNE Multimedia, Inc. (Here on referred to as NYNE) and its subsidiary companies respect the privacy rights of our online visitors and recognize the importance of protecting the information collected from you. We have adopted a corporate wide Online Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) that guides how we collect, store, and use the information you provide online.  Please note that this policy applies only to sites maintained by NYNE and its subsidiaries, and not to websites maintained by other companies or organizations to which we link.

**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**

**Our primary goals in collecting personally identifiable information are to provide you with the product and services made available through our website, including, but not limited to, our services, to communicate with you, and to manage your registered user account, if you have one.**

**INFORMATION COLLECTED UPON REGISTRATION**

If you desire to have access to certain restricted sections of our website, you will be required to become a registered user, and to submit certain personally identifiable information to NYNE. This happens in a number of instances, such as when you sign up for our services or if you desire to receive marketing materials and information. Personally identifiable information that we may collect in such instances may include your IP address, full user name, password, email address, city, time zone, telephone number, and other information that you decide to provide us with, or that you decide to include in your public profile.

**USE OF CONTACT INFORMATION**

In addition, we may use your contact information to market to you, and provide you with information about, our products and services. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such information or communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications.

**AdRoll**

Nyne works with [AdRoll retargeting](http://www.adroll.com/), who uses technology including web beacons and cookies to collect data about our website usage and to improve the effectiveness of our marketing. Data recorded through the use of this technology is aggregated and shared with us.

No personally identifiable information about you is collected or shared by AdRoll with Nyne. You can opt-out of AdRoll and their partners by visiting [this link](http://www.adroll.com/about/privacy).

**LOG DATA**

When you visit the Site, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website as Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type or the domain from which you are visiting, the websites you visit, the search terms you use, and any advertisements on which you click. For most users accessing the Internet from an Internet service provider the IP address will be different every time you log on. We use Log Data to monitor the use of the Site and of our Service, and for the Site’s technical administration. We do not associate your IP address with any other personally identifiable information to identify you personally, except in case of violation of the Terms of Service

**COOKIES**

We use cookies and other technologies to passively collect demographic information, personalize your experience on our site and monitor advertisements and other activities. Cookies are small files downloaded to your computer to track movements within websites. We may link cookie information to personal information. Cookies link to information regarding what items you have selected for purchase at our store or pages you have viewed. This information is used to keep track of your shopping cart and make sure you don’t see the same ad repeatedly. Also, we use cookies to deliver content specific to your interest and to monitor website usage. Some of our sites use an outside ad NYNE to display ads. These ads may contain cookies. Our ad companies collect cookies received with banner ads, and NYNE does not have access to this information. Most browsers are automatically set to accept cookies whenever you visit a website. You can disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent. However some areas of our sites will not function properly if you do so. Please note that this Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by NYNE only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**OTHER TECHNOLOGIES**

Other technologies used include clear GIF’s and IP address logging. Clear GIF’s also known as web bugs, beacons, or tags, are small graphic images placed on a web page, web-based document, or in an e-mail message. Clear GIF’s are invisible to the user because they are typically very small (only 1-by-1 pixel) and the same color as the background of the web page, document or e-mail message. We do not use clear GIF’s to collect personal information about you. However, we may use clear GIF’s to capture statistical usage information for our web pages, features, or other elements on a web page. We may correlate this information to a user to personalize user experience and for statistical analysis of user experiences on our web pages.
